http://www.dogquotations.com/privacy-policy.html

DogQuotations.com'sPrivacy Policy
I recognize that your privacy is important. This document outlines the types of personal information I receive and collect when you use DogQuotations.com, as well as some of the steps I take to safeguard information. I hope this will help you make an informed decision about sharing personal information with me.As the owner of DogQuotations.com, I strive to maintain the highest standards of decency, fairness and integrity in all my operations. Likewise, I am dedicated to protecting my customers', consumers' and online visitors' privacy on this site.
Personal Information
DogQuotations.com collects personally identifiable information from its visitors only on a voluntary basis. Personal information collected on a voluntary basis may include name, postal address, email address, company name and telephone number.This information is collected automatically if you request information from me, participate in a contest or sweepstakes, sign up to join an email list, or request some other service or information from me. I review the information collected internally. I use it to improve the content of my site, notify my visitors of updates, and respond to visitor inquiries.Once I have reviewed information, I discard it securely or store it in my files. If I make material changes in the collection of personally identifiable information, I will inform you by placing a notice on this site.I use personal information received from any visitor only for internal purposes and will not sell or provide it to third parties.
Use of Cookies and Web Beacons
I may use cookies to help you personalize your online experience. Cookies are identifiers transferred to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable my systems to recognize your browser.The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize the site's pages, or register with any of my site's services, a cookie enables DogQuotations.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser; however, if you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the site.A web beacon is a transparent image file used to monitor your journey around a single site or collection of sites. They are also referred to as web bugs. They are commonly used by sites that hire third-party services to monitor traffic. They may be used in association with cookies to understand how visitors interact with the pages and content on the pages of a site.I may serve third-party advertisements that use cookies and web beacons to ascertain how many times you've seen an advertisement. I do not give any of your personally identifiable information to ad providers for cookie or web beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information on this site.You can set your browser to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. You can use privacy software to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions shouldn't cause a problem with my site, should you so choose.
Children's Online Privacy Protection Act
This site is directed to adults; it is not directed to children under the age of 13. I operate my site in compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, and do not knowingly collect or use personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.
Non-Personal Information
In some cases, I may collect information about you that is not personally identifiable. I use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about my user base as a whole. I use this information solely for internal review and do not share it with other organizations for commercial purposes.
Release of Information
If I sell DogQuotations.com, the information I have obtained from you through your voluntary participation in this site may transfer to the new owner as a part of the sale so that the service being provided to you may continue.In that event, you will receive notice through this site of that change in control and practices, and I will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser honors any opt-out requests you might make.
How You Can Correct or Remove Information
I provide this privacy policy as a statement to you of my commitment to protect your personal information. If you have submitted personal information through this site and would like that information deleted from my records or would like to update or correct that information, please use my Contact page.
Updates and Effective Date
As the owner of DogQuotations.com, I reserve the right to make changes in this policy. If there is a material change in my privacy practices, I will indicate on this site that my privacy practices have changed, and will provide a link to the new privacy policy.I encourage you to periodically review this policy so that you will know what information I collect and how I use it.
Agreeing to Terms
If you do not agree to DogQuotations.com's Privacy Policy as posted here on this page, please do not use this site or any services offered by this site.Your use of this site indicates acceptance of this privacy policy.
Dog Quotations
›
Privacy Policy
HomeWrite a MemorialGrieving and LossRelish's UpdatesPuppy QuotesFamilies and KidsDogs and FriendshipRescuing DogsQuotes About MuttsCommunicatingBehaviour & TrainingCars and TravelTV and MoviesFunny Dog QuotesDogs and PoliticsHeads of State/RoyalsQuotes About AnimalsDog PoemsDog ProverbsBible Dog QuotesReligious Dog QuotesDog Quote VariationsDog Quotes, A to ZComments/ContactQuote SearchPrivacy Policy
Original content copyright © 2006– DogQuotations.comAll other content is in the public domain or is copyright by the credited author.
